
[{
  "id": "1",
  "imgFront": "src/assets/icons/back.svg",
  "imgBack": "src/assets/icons/css.svg",
  "target": "1"
}, {
  "id": "2",
  "imgFront": "src/assets/icons/back.svg",
  "imgBack": "src/assets/icons/html.svg",
  "target": "2"
}, {
  "id": "3",
  "imgFront": "src/assets/icons/back.svg",
  "imgBack": "src/assets/icons/js.svg",
  "target": "3"
}, {
  "id": "4",
  "imgFront": "src/assets/icons/back.svg",
  "imgBack": "src/assets/icons/php.svg",
  "target": "4"
}, {
  "id": "5",
  "imgFront": "src/assets/icons/back.svg",
  "imgBack": "src/assets/icons/sql.svg",
  "target": "5"
},
{
  "id": "6",
  "imgFront": "src/assets/icons/back.svg",
  "imgBack": "src/assets/icons/svg.svg",
  "target": "6"
}, {
  "id": "7",
  "imgFront": "src/assets/icons/back.svg",
  "imgBack": "src/assets/icons/txt.svg",
  "target": "7"
}, {
  "id": "8",
  "imgFront": "src/assets/icons/back.svg",
  "imgBack": "src/assets/icons/xls.svg",
  "target": "8"
}, {
  "id": "9",
  "imgFront": "src/assets/icons/back.svg",
  "imgBack": "src/assets/icons/zip.svg",
  "target": "9"
}, {
  "id": "10",
  "imgFront": "src/assets/icons/back.svg",
  "imgBack": "src/assets/icons/ps.svg",
  "target": "10"
},
{
  "id": "11",
  "imgFront": "src/assets/icons/back.svg",
  "imgBack": "src/assets/icons/css.svg",
  "target": "1"
}, {
  "id": "12",
  "imgFront": "src/assets/icons/back.svg",
  "imgBack": "src/assets/icons/html.svg",
  "target": "2"
}, {
  "id": "13",
  "imgFront": "src/assets/icons/back.svg",
  "imgBack": "src/assets/icons/js.svg",
  "target": "3"
}, {
  "id": "14",
  "imgFront": "src/assets/icons/back.svg",
  "imgBack": "src/assets/icons/php.svg",
  "target": "4"
}, {
  "id": "15",
  "imgFront": "src/assets/icons/back.svg",
  "imgBack": "src/assets/icons/sql.svg",
  "target": "5"
}, {
  "id": "16",
  "imgFront": "src/assets/icons/back.svg",
  "imgBack": "src/assets/icons/svg.svg",
  "target": "6"
}, {
  "id": "17",
  "imgFront": "src/assets/icons/back.svg",
  "imgBack": "src/assets/icons/txt.svg",
  "target": "7"
}, {
  "id": "18",
  "imgFront": "src/assets/icons/back.svg",
  "imgBack": "src/assets/icons/xls.svg",
  "target": "8"
}, {
  "id": "19",
  "imgFront": "src/assets/icons/back.svg",
  "imgBack": "src/assets/icons/zip.svg",
  "target": "9"
}, {
  "id": "20",
  "imgFront": "src/assets/icons/back.svg",
  "imgBack": "src/assets/icons/ps.svg",
  "target": "10"
}]


